<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<Defs>
	<Vehicles.VehicleBuildDef ParentName="VehicleBaseBuildable">
		<defName>CVNOVAdam_blueprint</defName>
		<label>overlord gunship:Adam</label>
		<description>Overlord-Adam Class, the smallest of the overlords, measuring generously at 7x7 meters, based off the designs of Adam Varkish, a mechanitor that believed fielding as many troops as possible was the best way, preferring to use lancers to overwhelm any target even aircraft.
Adam is capable of not only maintaining the most bandwith for only using a single HIve subcore, but also being able to ripscan downed humans to then gestate more soldiers on the go, creating a cruel cycle of battle. \n\n&lt;color=#FFA500&gt;Requires Missile hulls for rocket pods and Standardized mechanoid AP rounds for the shredder.&lt;/color&gt; \n\n&lt;color=#00ddc0&gt;Can do all the functions required of a mechanitor besides gestating and reviving heavy and ultraheavy mechanoids this is more a limitation of Adam's size, additionally being very weak to anti air means adam is not meant for frontline combat but can support.&lt;/color&gt; \n\n&lt;color=#FF0000&gt;Hostile Adams are very rare and often very dangerous accompanied by their prefered doctrine, With adams you'll find yourself swamped often with Scythers, Lancers and Militors.&lt;/color&gt;</description>
	
		<designationCategory>Biotech</designationCategory>
		
		<graphicData>
			<texPath>Things/Vehicles/Overlords/CVNOVAdam</texPath>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Multi</graphicClass>
			<drawSize>(7.5, 7.5)</drawSize>
		</graphicData>
		
		<rotatable>true</rotatable>

		<statBases>
			<MaxHitPoints>500</MaxHitPoints>
			<WorkToBuild>9000</WorkToBuild>
			<Flammability>0.5</Flammability>
		</statBases>
		
		<size>(7,7)</size>
		
		<researchPrerequisites>
			<li>UltraMechtech</li>
		</researchPrerequisites>
		
		<costList>
			<CVNMechComposite>10</CVNMechComposite>
			<ComponentIndustrial>15</ComponentIndustrial>
			<ComponentSpacer>10</ComponentSpacer>
			<SubcoreHigh>1</SubcoreHigh>
			<NanostructuringChip>1</NanostructuringChip>
			<SubcoreHive>1</SubcoreHive>
		</costList>
		
		<soundImpactDefault>BulletImpact_Metal</soundImpactDefault>
		<thingToSpawn>CVNOVAdam</thingToSpawn>
		
		<constructionSkillPrerequisite>6</constructionSkillPrerequisite>
	</Vehicles.VehicleBuildDef>
</Defs>
